widewalls.ch 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy | Widewalls

This Privacy Policy describes how Widewalls handles your personal information, and applies to the website [www.widewalls.ch](http://www.widewalls.ch/). 

This Policy is part of our Terms of Use. By accessing or using our Services in any way, you agree that your information may be collected, stored, shared, and used as described in this Policy and our Terms of Use. This Policy does not apply to any entity that we do not own or control, or to any person that we do not employ or manage.

### Collection and Use of Personal and Non-Personal Information

Widewalls may collect and store the following personal information, or any other information specified in this Privacy Policy:

• Information that you provide by filling out Widewalls forms: contact information, such as your name, email address, and other; this includes information provided at the time of registering, posting material, or requesting services;  
• Unique identifiers, such as username or password;  
• Link of your Widewalls account to your account on another social media service (including when you sign up for our Services through another social media service), in which case we may obtain your username on that service and other information you make publicly available through that service;  
If you provide it, Widewalls also collects the following non-personal information:  
• Information about your business, such as company name, company size, and business type;  
• Demographic information, such as age, education, gender, interests, and zip code;  
• Correspondence with other users and galleries that you send through Widewalls website, and correspondence sent to Widewalls;  
• Widewalls may keep a record of the correspondence if you [contact us](mailto:info@widewalls.ch).  
• Our Services may include features that enable you to choose your “favorite” artists, artwork, or other items. Our Services may also include features that enable you to “follow” galleries, institutions or other Users, artists, designers or other creators, or categories of artwork or other items. If your public profile is enabled, other Users may also be able to follow you, and the number of Users that follow you may be visible to other Users on our Services. You may be able to share, or choose not to share, certain information about your favorites, follows or followers on or through our Services, as indicated by us in connection with these features or in your profile and account settings.  
Widewalls, as most websites, automatically gathers information about your computer. Usually collected information is your IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. Widewalls does not, without your consent, sell, share, or rent this information to others for their marketing purposes. Widewalls may, in compliance with applicable law, combine your information with information lawfully acquired from other organizations, and use it to improve and personalize services, content, and advertising.

Widewalls may use this information in the following ways:  
• To provide you with information, products, services, or customer support that you request from us, as specified in this Privacy Policy  
• To allow you to participate in interactive features of Widewalls products or services, contests and sweepstakes, when you choose to do so  
• To prevent, discover, and investigate violations of applicable Terms and Conditions  
• To send product updates or Terms of Use information  
• To respond to customer service requests  
• To send you a newsletter and marketing announcements  
• To improve Widewalls website and marketing efforts  
• To conduct research and analysis

### Advertising Cookies

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.
  * Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

If you have not [opted out of third-party ad serving](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94152), the cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94149) may also be used to serve ads on widewalls.ch

  * widewalls.ch sets cookies from third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads.
  * You may visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising.

### Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving Widewalls newsletters or marketing emails at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions included in those communications, or you can [contact us](mailto:info@widewalls.ch).

### Request Information

You may at several different points on the Widewalls websites request information (e.g., how to become an advertiser, or how to become a member gallery). To submit a request using the forms provided on the website, you must supply contact information (e.g., name, email, phone number). This information is used by Widewalls to provide the information requested.

### Information Obtained from Third Parties

If you provide personal information about others, or if others give us your information, Widewalls will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided.

### Information Sharing

Widewalls will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy, without selling it to third parties.

Widewalls may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help with our business activities, such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services.

We may also disclose your personal information:  
• To help with business operations (such as fraud investigations, affiliate and rewards programs), to protect rights or safety, as required by law;  
• If Widewalls is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale; you will be notified via email and/or a notice on the website, before choosing what you can do with your personal information.  
• To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

Widewalls never shares your personal information with other companies so that they can market their products or services to you. 

Widewalls makes your contact information available to other users so that you can interact and complete a transaction.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Widewalls uses cookies on certain pages to help analyze webpage flow, customize services, content, and advertising, and measure promotional effectiveness.  
Important things to know about cookies:  
• You may disable cookies if your browser permits. The exact procedure will vary from browser to browser; check help section.  
• Widewalls offers certain features that are available only through the use of cookies. Widewalls also uses cookies in the Member Services area to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.  
• You may encounter cookies from third parties on certain pages (for example, advertisers), but Widewalls has no access to or control over these cookies  
Our third-party data analytics providers include but are not limited to Google Analytics. These providers help us to better understand how our Services and Content are accessed and used, which in turn helps us to develop and improve them. These providers may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to collect information about how Users access or engage with our Services, Content, emails, and ads on or off our Services. You may opt-out of receiving cookies from Google Analytics on their respective websites. If you opt-out of receiving cookies from one of these providers, it may place a cookie on your device to remember your preference. Accordingly, if you delete cookies, install a new browser, or start using a new device, you may need to repeat the opt-out process. You may opt-out of the use of cookies by visiting [Google’s Advertising and Privacy page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) .

### Log Files

Widewalls uses your IP address to help diagnose server problems, and to administer our website. Widewalls uses your IP addresses to analyze trends and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.  
Every time you access a Widewalls website, some data are temporarily stored and processed in a log file, such as anonymous IP addresses, the browser types, the recalled page, or the date and time of the recall. These data are only evaluated for statistical purposes, to help us diagnose problems with our servers, to administer our sites, or to improve our offer.

### Web beacons

Widewalls webpages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how the websites are used, and may be used in some emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows Widewalls to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

### Links to Other Websites

The Widewalls website include links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from that of Widewalls. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. Widewalls encourages you to carefully read the Privacy Policy of any website you visit.

### Like button

When you choose the Facebook "Like" button on the Widewalls website, you will not be directed to another site, you will remain on Widewalls.ch.

### Data Retention

Widewalls retains your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that Widewalls no longer use your information to provide you services, [contact us](mailto:info@widewalls.ch). Widewalls will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Monitoring of Communications

Widewalls may review correspondence between users which is sent via Widewalls website, mobile application, or services in order to investigate violations of the Widewalls Terms of Service. Widewalls will only access such correspondence if it has a basis to believe that such terms are being violated. See the Widewalls [Terms of Service](https://www.widewalls.ch/terms-of-service/) for further information.

### Gallery Clients

As a member of Widewalls Galleries Network, you can ask Widewalls to review or retrieve emails sent to your gallery. Widewalls will access these emails only to provide these services for you.

### Security

When Widewalls collects personal information directly from you, it follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted: both during transmission and once received it is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Widewalls does its best to protect your personal data. Once your information is received, Widewalls uses strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore its absolute security cannot be guaranteed; any transmission is at your own risk. If you have any questions about security on the Widewalls website, [contact us](mailto:info@widewalls.ch). Widewalls has a company wide commitment to your privacy. To make sure your personal information is secure, please check that you are visiting Widewalls website.

### Additional Policy Information

Widewalls website include widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on website to provide specific services from another company (e.g., displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through a widget. Cookies may also be set by a widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this widget is governed by the Privacy Policy of the company that created it.

### Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire Widewalls services, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or deactivate it by making the change on the member information page  
You can also e-mail us, and Widewalls will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

### Note to Parents or Guardians

Minors may want to visit Widewalls on the Internet. However, the site is not directed at children under the age of 18, and those under the age of 18 should not provide personal data on the site unless they have received permission from their parents before submitting any personal information. Widewalls believes parents should be responsible for supervising the online activities of their children, and take into account various tools that allow them to provide their children with a controlled, child-friendly Internet. These tools are designed to preclude children from releasing personal information online without the permission of their parents. If Widewalls becomes aware that a minor has submitted information on its site, Widewalls reserves the right to request proof that the parent or guardian has permitted use by the minor of the site; otherwise Widewalls reserves the right to delete the relevant information and the minor's registration on the site.

### Notification of Privacy Policy Changes

Our business changes with time, and our Privacy Policy will change also. We reserve the right to change this Policy, without prior notice, at any time. All changes to this Policy will be effective when posted on our Services, or at such later date as may be specified in the updated Policy. We will notify you of any changes to this Policy by posting the updated Policy on our Services, and you agree to review this Policy regularly and inform yourself of all applicable changes.

### How to Contact Us

Widewalls is responsible for the personal data collected from users of this website and determines the purposes and means by which such personal data are used, subject to applicable law.  
If you have any questions about the Widewalls Privacy Policy or the practices of this site, please contact Customer Support via email [info@widewalls.ch](mailto:info@widewalls.ch).
